hitrader.com 2014-06-25

# Hitrader -- World-class trader’s community and new generation of investment platform

  * ###### Personal Information 

When you apply for or maintain a Hitrader Demo or Live account, we collect personal information about you for business purposes; to evaluate your financial needs, to process your requests and transactions, to inform you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and to provide client service. Such information may include: 

    * Application Information - Information that you provide to us on applications and other forms: your name, address, date of birth , social security number, occupation, assets, and income. 

    * Transaction Information - Information about your transactions with us or our affiliates, as well as information regarding our communications with you. Examples: your account balances, trading activity, your inquiries and our responses. 

    * Verification Information - Information necessary to verify your identity such as a passport or drivers license. Examples: background information about you we receive from public records or from other entities not affiliated with Hitrader. 

  * ###### Cookies 

Cookies are small files containing information that a website utilizes to track its visitors. Hitrader may set and access Hitrader cookies on your computer, enabling us to discover which advertisements and promotions bring users to our website. Hitrader or any of its divisions may use cookies in connection with Hitrader's products and services and to track your activities on our websites. The information that is collected and shared is anonymous and not personally identifiable. 

  * ###### Security Technology 

Hitrader uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to protect the information that you submit. This technology protects Users from having their information intercepted by anyone other than Hitrader during transmission. We work hard to ensure that our websites are secure and that they meet industry standards. We also use additional safeguards: firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers) and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data. 

  * ###### Sharing Information with Our Affiliates 

As permitted by applicable law, we may share the personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes; such as servicing client accounts and informing clients about new products and services. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by ZuluTrade, as well as companies which have an ownership interest in our company. The information we share with affiliates may include any of the information described above: your name, address, account information, etc. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent that ZuluTrade does in accordance with this Policy. 

  * ###### Sharing Information with Third-Parties 

With the exception of the purposes described in this Policy, Hitrader does not disclose personal information to third-parties. Third-party disclosures may include: sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with Hitrader; including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to Hitrader. Non-affiliated companies that assist Hitrader in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes which Hitrader dictates. We may also disclose your personal information to third-parties in order to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your express consent. Hitrader will not sell your personal information. 

  * ###### Regulatory Disclosure 

Under limited circumstances, Hitrader may disclose your personal information to third-parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. Hitrader may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities, law enforcement agencies, to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect Hitrader’s rights or property. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, your personal information will not be used for any other purpose unless we explicitly describe in what manner such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission. 

  * ###### Opt Out 

You are not required to supply any of the personal information that we may request. However, failure to do so may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account or to provide services to you. While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any changes to your personal information. If you do not wish to have your personal information disclosed to third parties as described in this Policy, please contact us via e-mail. 

  * ###### Risk Disclaimer 

HITRADER INC - Past performance posted by Systems Providers (Providers), is not necessarily indicative of future results. No representation is made that any account is likely to achieve profits or losses similar to those shown. In fact, there are frequently sharp differences between hypothetical performance results and the actual results subsequently achieved by any particularly trading program.  
The composite monthly results are primarily hypothetical results of the master demo and its representation of the Providers, though performance results displayed may represent a combination of live and hypothetical results and are not exclusive to either. There are numerous other factors related to markets in general or to the implementation of any specific trading program that cannot be fully accounted for in the preparation of hypothetical performance results and all of which can adversely affect actual trading results. There is no guarantee that one applying these methodologies would have the same results as the hypothetically posted. Since trading successfully depends on many elements including but not limited to a trading methodology and a trader's own psychology, the web site does not make any representation whatsoever that the above mentioned trading systems might be or are suitable or that they would be profitable for you. 

  * Please realize the risk with any investment and consult investment professionals before proceeding. The trading systems herein described have been developed for sophisticated traders who fully understand the nature and the scope of the risks that are associated with trading. Should you decide to trade any or all of these systems' signals, it is your decision.
